const availableCategories = [
  "Sports & Leisure",
  "Society & Culture",
  "Science",
  "Music",
  "History",
  "Geography",
  "General knowledge",
  "Food & Drink",
  "Film & TV",
  "Arts & Literature",
];

const sportsLeisure = [
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417d1c0f96c4efe8d773a5",
    correctAnswer: "Edmonton Oilers",
    allOptions: [
      "Edmonton Oilers",
      "Edmonton Steelers",
      "Edmonton Eathquakes",
      "Edmonton Padres",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is a hockey team based in Edmonton?",
    tags: ["canada", "hockey", "nhl"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417d480f96c4efe8d773b7",
    correctAnswer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
    allOptions: [
      "Milwaukee Heat",
      "Milwaukee Reds",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Milwaukee Pirates",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is a basketball team based in Milwaukee?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417dc50f96c4efe8d773e8",
    correctAnswer: "Toronto Raptors",
    allOptions: [
      "Toronto Football",
      "Toronto Islanders",
      "Toronto Falcons",
      "Toronto Raptors",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is a basketball team based in Toronto?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f893",
    correctAnswer: "Volleyball",
    allOptions: ["Cycling", "Volleyball", "Golf", "Rugby Union"],
    question: "With which sport is Karch Kiraly associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417da50f96c4efe8d773db",
    correctAnswer: "San Francisco 49ers",
    allOptions: [
      "San Francisco Jaguars",
      "San Francisco 49ers",
      "San Francisco Pistons",
      "San Francisco Predators",
    ],
    question:
      "Which of these is an American Football team based in San Francisco?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f89c",
    correctAnswer: "Baseball",
    allOptions: ["Baseball", "Rugby Union", "Table tennis", "Cricket"],
    question: "With which sport is Jackie Robinson associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417d250f96c4efe8d773a9",
    correctAnswer: "Houston Rockets",
    allOptions: [
      "Houston Thunder",
      "Houston A's",
      "Houston Sounders",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is a basketball team based in Houston?",
    tags: ["basketball", "nba", "usa"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500e2",
    correctAnswer: "8",
    allOptions: ["5", "14", "20", "8"],
    question: "How many fighters are playable in 'Street Fighter II'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500c2",
    correctAnswer: "15",
    allOptions: ["21", "15", "25", "20"],
    question: "How many points win a game in badminton?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500aa",
    correctAnswer: "300",
    allOptions: ["100", "200", "300", "250"],
    question:
      "In tenpin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f875",
    correctAnswer: "Tennis",
    allOptions: ["Gymnastics", "Cycling", "Swimming", "Tennis"],
    question: "With which sport is Rafael Nadal associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8b3",
    correctAnswer: "Athletics",
    allOptions: ["Volleyball", "Athletics", "Cricket", "Cycling"],
    question: "With which sport is Jesse Owens associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "6242e81d8c2538f9601d2f95",
    correctAnswer: "The Eagles",
    allOptions: ["The Bluebirds", "The Sky Blues", "The Rams", "The Eagles"],
    question:
      "What is the nickname of the English football team Crystal Palace?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62399eeb43254f1dbcdd082d",
    correctAnswer: "Brazil",
    allOptions: ["Brazil", "France", "Germany", "Uruguay"],
    question:
      "Which country won the 1994 FIFA World Cup, hosted in United States?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "6242e8238c2538f9601d2f97",
    correctAnswer: "The Whites",
    allOptions: ["The Reds", "The Terriers", "The Eagles", "The Whites"],
    question: "What is the nickname of the English football team Leeds United?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417cc88c3137686862d73a",
    correctAnswer: "Baltimore Ravens",
    allOptions: [
      "Baltimore Blues",
      "Baltimore Crew",
      "Baltimore Ravens",
      "Baltimore Wizards",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is an American Football team based in Baltimore?",
    tags: ["football", "american_football", "baltimore", "nfl", "usa"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "62417d890f96c4efe8d773d1",
    correctAnswer: "Phoenix Suns",
    allOptions: [
      "Phoenix Union",
      "Phoenix Heat",
      "Phoenix Bears",
      "Phoenix Suns",
    ],
    question: "Which of these is a basketball team based in Phoenix?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8a8",
    correctAnswer: "Golf",
    allOptions: ["Golf", "Table tennis", "Swimming", "Rowing"],
    question: "With which sport is Tiger Woods associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8b4",
    correctAnswer: "Football",
    allOptions: ["Golf", "Tennis", "Football", "Badminton"],
    question: "With which sport is Johan Cruyff associated?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Sport & Leisure",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950024",
    correctAnswer: "Tennis",
    allOptions: ["Soccer", "Badminton", "Volleyball", "Tennis"],
    question: "With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified?",
    tags: ["people"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const societyCulture = [
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fce6",
    correctAnswer: "Austroasiatic",
    allOptions: ["Uralic", "Austroasiatic", "Sino-Tibetan", "Kraâ€“Dai"],
    question: "The language 'Vietnamese' belongs to which language family?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd01",
    correctAnswer: "W. K. Clifford",
    allOptions: [
      "Thomas Hobbes",
      "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
      "Epictetus",
      "W. K. Clifford",
    ],
    question:
      "Which philosopher famously said 'It is wrong always, everywhere and for everyone, to believe anything upon insufficient evidence'?",
    tags: ["quotes", "philosophy"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950124",
    correctAnswer: "In the beginning",
    allOptions: [
      "Praise the lord",
      "In the beginning",
      "Let there be",
      "Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!",
    ],
    question: "What are the first three words of The Bible?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95012f",
    correctAnswer: "Bull",
    allOptions: ["Horse", "Dolphin", "Eagle", "Bull"],
    question: "In what animal form did Zeus seduce Europa?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95012c",
    correctAnswer: "December",
    allOptions: ["December", "September", "April", "November"],
    question: "In what month is Christmas observed?",
    tags: ["christmas", "general_knowledge"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fca5",
    correctAnswer: "Afroasiatic",
    allOptions: ["Afroasiatic", "Indo-European", "Turkic", "Dravidian"],
    question:
      "The language 'Sanaani Spoken Arabic' belongs to which language family?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95013d",
    correctAnswer: "Isis",
    allOptions: ["Set", "Ammit", "Horus", "Isis"],
    question: "In Egyptian mythology, who was Horus' mother?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd2c",
    correctAnswer: "Bertrand Russell",
    allOptions: [
      "Thomas Hobbes",
      "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
      "Bertrand Russell",
      "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
    ],
    question:
      "Which philosopher famously said 'It is undesirable to believe a proposition when there is no ground whatever for supposing it true'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950131",
    correctAnswer: "Narcissus",
    allOptions: ["Hercules", "Narcissus", "Apollo", "Perseus"],
    question:
      "In Greek mythology, who was the beautiful young man Echo fell in love with?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd10",
    correctAnswer: "Jean-Paul Sartre",
    allOptions: [
      "Thomas Hobbes",
      "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
      "Jean-Paul Sartre",
      "G. W. F. Hegel",
    ],
    question: "Which philosopher famously said 'Man is condemned to be free'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950123",
    correctAnswer: "Evil",
    allOptions: ["Shame", "Jewellery", "Mystery", "Evil"],
    question: "What did Pandora release when she opened the box?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcb1",
    correctAnswer: "Indo-European",
    allOptions: ["Turkic", "Indo-European", "Nigerâ€“Congo", "Austronesian"],
    question: "The language 'Assamese' belongs to which language family?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd32",
    correctAnswer: "Gottfried Wilhelm Leibniz",
    allOptions: [
      "Thomas Hobbes",
      "Denis Diderot",
      "Ludwig Wittgenstein",
      "Gottfried Wilhelm Leibniz",
    ],
    question:
      "Which philosopher famously said 'We live in the best of all possible worlds'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fce0",
    correctAnswer: "Sino-Tibetan",
    allOptions: ["Sino-Tibetan", "Japonic", "Uralic", "Kraâ€“Dai"],
    question: "The language 'Hakka' belongs to which language family?",
    tags: ["language"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500ee",
    correctAnswer: "Fortuna",
    allOptions: ["Tyche", "Fortuna", "Jupiter", "Vesta"],
    question: "Who is the Roman goddess of destiny?",
    tags: ["romans", "mythology", "classics"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950127",
    correctAnswer: "Longinus",
    allOptions: ["Atticus", "Augustus", "Longinus", "Tiberius"],
    question:
      "Which Roman soldier pierced the crucified Christ on His side with his spear.",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95010a",
    correctAnswer: "Oxford University",
    allOptions: ["Oxford University", "Jerusalem", "Cape Town", "Bethlehem"],
    question: "Where was Methodism founded?",
    tags: ["religion"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950101",
    correctAnswer: "Zeus",
    allOptions: ["Hephaestus", "Agamemnon", "Achilles", "Zeus"],
    question: "Who was Hercules' father?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500e5",
    correctAnswer: "Dionysus",
    allOptions: ["Aphrodite", "Isis", "Bacchus", "Dionysus"],
    question: "Who was the Greek god of wine?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Society & Culture",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcb7",
    correctAnswer: "Indo-European",
    allOptions: ["Sino-Tibetan", "Indo-European", "Turkic", "Nigerâ€“Congo"],
    question: "The language 'Greek' belongs to which language family?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const science = [
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510e2",
    correctAnswer: "Wind",
    allOptions: ["Boat", "Wind", "Horse", "Tree"],
    question: 'A "sirocco" refers to a type of __________."',
    tags: ["words"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510bb",
    correctAnswer: "Jurassic",
    allOptions: ["Mesozoic", "Triassic", "Devonian", "Jurassic"],
    question: "In Geology What Period followed The Cretaceous?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95109f",
    correctAnswer: "Stork",
    allOptions: ["Stork", "Pelican", "Flamingo", "Swan"],
    question:
      "The shoebill __________, native to Africa, is often compared to a statue. The bird will stand perfectly still for long periods waiting for fish to come to surface in the water.",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9505a2",
    correctAnswer: "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions",
    allOptions: [
      "existence",
      "dreams",
      "plant nutrition and growth in relation to soil conditions",
      "the study or knowledge of emetics",
    ],
    question: "What is Agrobiology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "62433548cfaae40c12961498",
    correctAnswer: "A Ram",
    allOptions: ["A Jack", "A Drake", "A Rooster", "A Ram"],
    question: "What would you call a male sheep?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "62433564cfaae40c129614a3",
    correctAnswer: "A Cob",
    allOptions: ["A Cob", "A Hob", "A Tiercel", "A Macho"],
    question: "What would you call a male swan?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504c2",
    correctAnswer: "one of two main branches of soil science",
    allOptions: [
      "wood",
      "Unidentified flying object phenomena",
      "microorganisms",
      "one of two main branches of soil science",
    ],
    question: "What is Pedology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950479",
    correctAnswer: "religion",
    allOptions: [
      "religion",
      "measurement",
      "children's behavior and development",
      "blood serum",
    ],
    question: "What is Theology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3f7cc59eab6f9523cc",
    correctAnswer: "Bactrian",
    allOptions: ["Dromedary", "Alpine", "Bactrian", "Bolo"],
    question: "What type of camel has two humps?",
    tags: ["animals", "biology"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f950fd8",
    correctAnswer: "Kidney",
    allOptions: ["Liver", "Lung", "Kidney", "Brain"],
    question: "Which vital organ does the adjective renal refer to?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951935",
    correctAnswer: "Radio Carbon Dating",
    allOptions: [
      "Radio Carbon Dating",
      "Olfactory Dating",
      "Magnetic Resonance Dating",
      "Natural Decayance Dating",
    ],
    question: "What Process Is Used For Dating Ancient Organic Objects?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951089",
    correctAnswer: "Pleiades",
    allOptions: ["Perseids", "Nymphoids", "Sorestas", "Pleiades"],
    question: "Which cluster of stars is also known as the Seven Sisters?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950539",
    correctAnswer: "the fetus, especially when within the uterus",
    allOptions: [
      "the future",
      "the study and psychology of organisms with regard to their functions and structures",
      "the fetus, especially when within the uterus",
      "bryophytes",
    ],
    question: "What is Fetology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f9510e4",
    correctAnswer: "11 days",
    allOptions: ["11 weeks", "11 hours", "11 days", "11 months"],
    question:
      "Adult polar bears usually eat just the skin and blubber of a seal. They leave the meat for cubs and scavengers. One seal will sustain an adult bear for __________",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "624334c1cfaae40c12961463",
    correctAnswer: "A Calf",
    allOptions: ["A Caterpillar", "A Kit", "A Lamb", "A Calf"],
    question: "What is the word for a young moose?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95109a",
    correctAnswer: "Shark",
    allOptions: ["Shark", "Whale", "Dolphin", "Orca"],
    question: "The fins of what sea creature are made into a soup?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f95057f",
    correctAnswer: "the heart",
    allOptions: [
      "past cultures through the analysis of material remains",
      "the heart",
      "Japanese people",
      "ends or final causes",
    ],
    question: "What is Cardiology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504a4",
    correctAnswer:
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract",
    allOptions: [
      "fossil footprints, tracks and burrows",
      "classification",
      "the mathematical study of closeness and connectedness",
      "the specialty in medicine that deals with diseases of the lungs and the respiratory tract",
    ],
    question: "What is Pulmonology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950505",
    correctAnswer: "waves or wave motions",
    allOptions: [
      "weather",
      "Tibet",
      "waves or wave motions",
      "mental processes in living creatures",
    ],
    question: "What is Kymatology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Science",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f95048c",
    correctAnswer: "the effect of evolution on ethology",
    allOptions: [
      "the medical study of the causation of disease",
      "snakes",
      "wonders, or monsters",
      "the effect of evolution on ethology",
    ],
    question: "What is Sociobiology the study of?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const music = [
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fba8",
    correctAnswer: '"Sympathy for the Devil" by the Rolling Stones',
    allOptions: [
      '"Welcome to the Black Parade" by My Chemical Romance',
      '"Crazy Train" by Ozzy Osbourne',
      '"Baby Got Back" by Sir Mix-a-Lot',
      '"Sympathy for the Devil" by the Rolling Stones',
    ],
    question:
      "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Please allow me to introduce myself / I'm a man of wealth and taste / I've been around for a long, long year / Stole many a man's soul and faith...\"?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94feb5",
    correctAnswer: "BeyoncÃ©",
    allOptions: ["Madonna", "Drake", "Nicki Minaj", "BeyoncÃ©"],
    question:
      "Which American singer, actress and record producer released the studio album '4'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950da4",
    correctAnswer: "Led Zeppelin",
    allOptions: ["Led Zeppelin", "Cocteau Twins", "Lostprophets", "The Kinks"],
    question: "Which band includes 'John Bonham'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d7c",
    correctAnswer: "Judas Priest",
    allOptions: [
      "Arctic Monkeys",
      "Judas Priest",
      "Feeder",
      "Bring Me the Horizon",
    ],
    question: "Which band includes 'Rob Halford'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b63",
    correctAnswer: "Big Bang",
    allOptions: ["Red Velvet", "2PM", "Big Bang", "BTS"],
    question: "Which band includes 'G-Dragon'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cf1",
    correctAnswer: "Queen",
    allOptions: ["Level 42", "Queen", "Deep Purple", "Feeder"],
    question: "Which British rock band released the album 'Made in Heaven'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdd3",
    correctAnswer: "Ed Sheeran",
    allOptions: ["Mika", "Morrissey", "Dido", "Ed Sheeran"],
    question: "Which English singer-songwriter released the studio album 'Ã·'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b7a",
    correctAnswer: "The Offspring",
    allOptions: [
      "The Offspring",
      "Styx",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
      "The Velvet Underground",
    ],
    question:
      "Which punk band from the United States released the studio album 'Rise and Fall, Rage and Grace'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950da1",
    correctAnswer: "Iron Maiden",
    allOptions: ["Deep Purple", "Feeder", "Squeeze", "Iron Maiden"],
    question: "Which band includes 'Adrian Smith'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff64",
    correctAnswer: "Queen",
    allOptions: ["Feeder", "The Clash", "Queen", "Pink Floyd"],
    question:
      "Which British rock band released the single 'Another One Bites the Dust'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d50",
    correctAnswer: "One Direction",
    allOptions: [
      "One Direction",
      "Level 42",
      "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark",
      "Blur",
    ],
    question: "Which band includes 'Louis Tomlinson'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b9e",
    correctAnswer: "Wings",
    allOptions: ["Level 42", "Deep Purple", "The Chemical Brothers", "Wings"],
    question: "Which band includes 'Paul McCartney'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c7d",
    correctAnswer: "Eagles",
    allOptions: ["Led Zeppelin", "Black Sabbath", "Eagles", "Aerosmith"],
    question: "'Witchy Woman' was a hit for which rock group in the 1970's?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdd0",
    correctAnswer: "Megadeath",
    allOptions: ["Metallica", "Megadeath", "Slayer", "Sodom"],
    question: "Name The Thrash Metal Band Headed By Guitarist Dave Mustaine",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b74",
    correctAnswer: "Van Halen",
    allOptions: [
      "Deep Purple",
      "The Pussycat Dolls",
      "Van Halen",
      "Three 6 Mafia",
    ],
    question: "Which American heavy metal band released the song 'Jump'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b0a",
    correctAnswer: "Matia Bazar",
    allOptions: [
      "Matia Bazar",
      "Elio e le Storie Tese",
      "Wess and Dori Ghezzi",
      "Litfiba",
    ],
    question: "Which band includes 'Antonella Ruggiero'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbab",
    correctAnswer: '"Lose Yourself" by Eminem',
    allOptions: [
      "\"Jumpin', Jumpin'\" by Destiny's Child",
      '"What I Got" by Sublime',
      '"Basket Case" by Green Day',
      '"Lose Yourself" by Eminem',
    ],
    question:
      'Which song begins with the lyrics: "Look / If you had / One shot / Or one opportunity / To seize everything you ever wanted / In one moment / Would you capture it / Or just let it slip?"?',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d91",
    correctAnswer: "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
    allOptions: [
      "The Monkees",
      "Black Flag",
      "Journey",
      "Red Hot Chili Peppers",
    ],
    question: "Which band includes 'Anthony Kiedis'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950458",
    correctAnswer: "A Button",
    allOptions: ["A Carrot", "Snow", "A Button", "An Icicle"],
    question:
      "According to the lyrics of the famous Christmas song, what was Frosty The Snowman's nose made from?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Music",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b0d",
    correctAnswer: "Tangerine Dream",
    allOptions: ["Scooter", "Grave Digger", "Oomph!", "Tangerine Dream"],
    question: "Which band includes 'Klaus Schulze'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const history = [
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a16",
    correctAnswer: "Marc Antony",
    allOptions: ["Marc Antony", "Lepidus", "Marcus Crassus", "Pompey"],
    question: "Which Roman killed himself after his defeat at Actium?",
    tags: ["battles", "romans", "people"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a2d",
    correctAnswer: "Parthenon",
    allOptions: ["Colosseum", "Vivarium", "Academy", "Parthenon"],
    question: "Which of these is a building in the acropolis of Athens?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f9519b2",
    correctAnswer: "Radiation poisoning",
    allOptions: [
      "Drowning",
      "She was hit by a car",
      "Radiation poisoning",
      "She was struck by lightning",
    ],
    question: "What did Marie Curie die of on 4th July, 1934?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503c3",
    correctAnswer: "Raoul",
    allOptions: ["Pedro", "Raoul", "Mikel", "Sergio"],
    question: "What's fidel castro's brother's name? ",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950344",
    correctAnswer: "Catherine Of Aragon",
    allOptions: [
      "Anne Boleyn",
      "Anne Howard",
      "Catherine Of Aragon",
      "Catherine Parr",
    ],
    question: "Who Was The 1st wife of henry VIII? ",
    tags: ["kings", "uk", "medieval", "middle_ages", "people"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950439",
    correctAnswer: "Nine",
    allOptions: ["One", "Two", "Six", "Nine"],
    question: "How Many Crusades Were There?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951ac4",
    correctAnswer: "Calypso",
    allOptions: ["Calypso", "Discovery", "Terra Nova", "Beagle"],
    question: "What was the name of Jacques Cousteau's research ship?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951b37",
    correctAnswer: "1789",
    allOptions: ["1890", "1921", "1712", "1789"],
    question: "In What Year Was The French Declaration Of The Rights Of Man?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951bef",
    correctAnswer: "General Custer",
    allOptions: [
      "General Lee",
      "General Grant",
      "General Custer",
      "General Nelson",
    ],
    question: "Who was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95037b",
    correctAnswer: "Henry II",
    allOptions: ["William I", "Richard III", "Henry II", "Henry VIII"],
    question: 'Who Said "Will No-One Rid Me Of This Turbulent Priest"?',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd41",
    correctAnswer: "Constantine",
    allOptions: ["Constantine", "Byzantine", "Marcus Aurelius", "Trajan"],
    question:
      "Which Roman Emperor moved the capital from Rome to the city now known as Istanbul? ",
    tags: ["romans", "classics"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503f5",
    correctAnswer: "Hawaii",
    allOptions: ["Alaska", "Puerto Rico", "New Mexico", "Hawaii"],
    question: "What Became America's 50th State On August 21st 1959?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950320",
    correctAnswer: "Gamal Abdul Nasser",
    allOptions: [
      "Gamal Abdul Nasser",
      "Ahmed Sabzi",
      "Omar Sharif",
      "Asser Yasin",
    ],
    question:
      "Who was the President of Egypt in 1956 who nationalized the Suez Canal, causing British and French troops to invade the region?",
    tags: ["wars", "politics"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9aa",
    correctAnswer: "Elizabeth I",
    allOptions: ["James II", "Richard I", "Henry II", "Elizabeth I"],
    question:
      "Who was the monarch of England during the time period 1558-1603?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950437",
    correctAnswer: "The Royal Family",
    allOptions: [
      "The Kardashians",
      "The Osmonds",
      "The Royal Family",
      "The Gibbs",
    ],
    question:
      "In 1969 Richard Cawston Made A Documentary For The BBC About Which Famous Family?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a41",
    correctAnswer: "Ghana",
    allOptions: ["Ghana", "India", "Australia", "Egypt"],
    question:
      "The Gold Coast gained its independence from Great Britain in 1957 and formed part of which new country?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95036d",
    correctAnswer: "Marie Antoinette",
    allOptions: [
      "Queen Victoria",
      "Abraham Lincoln",
      "Marie Antoinette",
      "Cleopatra",
    ],
    question: 'Who is reputed to have said said: "Let them eat cake"?',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950357",
    correctAnswer: "George A. Custer",
    allOptions: [
      "Erwin Rommel",
      "Hannibal",
      "William T. Sherman",
      "George A. Custer",
    ],
    question: "Who was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95031c",
    correctAnswer: "Boudica",
    allOptions: ["Joan of Arc", "Zenobia", "Fulvia", "Boudica"],
    question:
      "Who Was the Queen Of The Iceni Tribe Of England Who Led An Uprising Against The Romans?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950347",
    correctAnswer: "Dwight Eisenhower",
    allOptions: [
      "Franklin Roosevelt",
      "Dwight Eisenhower",
      "Lyndon Johnson",
      "Jimmy Carter",
    ],
    question: "Who was President of the USA from 1953 till 1961?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const geography = [
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "623741c3cb85f7ce9e949d87",
    correctAnswer: "Norway",
    allOptions: ["Finland", "Norway", "Sweden", "Denmark"],
    question: "Oslo is the capital city of which country?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffa9",
    correctAnswer: "Venice",
    allOptions: ["Rome", "Milan", "Venice", "Naples"],
    question: "In which city would you find the Bridge of Sighs?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f9507f5",
    correctAnswer: "Oceania",
    allOptions: ["South America", "Oceania", "Europe", "Asia"],
    question: "The country of Samoa is on which continent?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a1a",
    correctAnswer: "France",
    allOptions: ["France", "Luxembourg", "Denmark", "Switzerland"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders Kingdom of the Netherlands?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f950000",
    correctAnswer: "Burkina Faso",
    allOptions: ["Ghana", "Mali", "Togo", "Burkina Faso"],
    question: "Ouagadougou is the capital of ______?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "623742becb85f7ce9e949dec",
    correctAnswer: "Funafuti",
    allOptions: ["Sana'a", "Funafuti", "Manama", "Kigali"],
    question: "What is the capital city of Tuvalu?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62373fc0cb85f7ce9e949cb8",
    correctAnswer: "Brasilia",
    allOptions: ["SÃ£o Paulo", "Rio de Janeiro", "Brasilia", "Manaus"],
    question: "What is the capital city of Brazil?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62374186cb85f7ce9e949d6f",
    correctAnswer: "Mozambique",
    allOptions: [
      "Burkina Faso",
      "Sao Tome and Principe",
      "Micronesia",
      "Mozambique",
    ],
    question: "Maputo is the capital city of which country?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "6237373ccfe13103f55eb5a0",
    correctAnswer: "Zimbabwe",
    allOptions: ["Zambia", "The Netherlands", "Zimbabwe", "Western Sahara"],
    question:
      "Which region of the world uses '.zw' at the end of its web addresses?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ffdd",
    correctAnswer: "Bamako",
    allOptions: ["Bamako", "Dakar", "Accra", "Kumasi"],
    question: "What is the capital of Mali?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "623388210161109f922aac69",
    correctAnswer: "International Date Line",
    allOptions: [
      "The Equator",
      "The Prime Meridian",
      "The Blood Meridian",
      "International Date Line",
    ],
    question:
      "Which imaginery line approximately follows the 180 degree meridian through the Pacific Ocean?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "623b585cfd6c701a921183b4",
    correctAnswer: "Indonesia",
    allOptions: ["Tanzania", "Indonesia", "Malta", "Brazil"],
    question:
      "In which country would you find the UNESCO World Heritage site of Prambanan?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a05",
    correctAnswer: "Saudi Arabia",
    allOptions: ["Djibouti", "Somalia", "Saudi Arabia", "Eritrea"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders Yemen?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdf2",
    correctAnswer: "Plate TectonicsÂ ",
    allOptions: [
      "Tectologic Deformation",
      "Terra Firma",
      "Terestial Convection",
      "Plate TectonicsÂ ",
    ],
    question: "Which Theory Is Used To Explain Continental Drift?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a83",
    correctAnswer: "Bolivia",
    allOptions: ["Trinidad and Tobago", "Chile", "Bolivia", "Grenada"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders Brazil?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62374029cb85f7ce9e949ce2",
    correctAnswer: "Nicosia",
    allOptions: ["Nicosia", "Riga", "Dodoma", "Port-au-Prince"],
    question: "What is the capital city of Cyprus?",
    tags: ["capital_cities"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950ab5",
    correctAnswer: "Ukraine",
    allOptions: ["Kyrgyzstan", "Ukraine", "Tajikistan", "Uzbekistan"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders Russia?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950acd",
    correctAnswer: "Bhutan",
    allOptions: ["Tajikistan", "Kyrgyzstan", "Bhutan", "Thailand"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders India?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "622a1c387cc59eab6f950a6e",
    correctAnswer: "Italy",
    allOptions: ["Croatia", "Italy", "San Marino", "Bosnia and Herzegovina"],
    question: "Which of these countries borders Austria?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: "62373600cfe13103f55eb590",
    correctAnswer: "United Arab Emirates",
    allOptions: ["United Arab Emirates", "Faeroe Islands", "Israel", "Armenia"],
    question:
      "Which region of the world uses '.ae' at the end of its web addresses?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const generalKnowledge = [
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c3a",
    correctAnswer: "Testicles",
    allOptions: ["Eyes", "Fists", "Arms", "Testicles"],
    question:
      "'Christmas Crackers' is cockney rhyming slang for which body part?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951043",
    correctAnswer: "Lesser Lion",
    allOptions: ["Iron Lion", "Lesser Lion", "Ferocious Lion", "Brave Lion"],
    question:
      "What is the meaning of the name of the constellation Leo Minor ?",
    tags: ["astronomy"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f95045c",
    correctAnswer: "7 Swans A Swimming",
    allOptions: [
      "7 Maids a Milking",
      "7 Lords A Leaping",
      "7 Drummers Drumming",
      "7 Swans A Swimming",
    ],
    question:
      'What did my true love give to me on the "Seventh" day of Christmas"?',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950fb2",
    correctAnswer: "The Lumiere Brothers",
    allOptions: [
      "The Lumiere Brothers",
      "The Warner Brothers",
      "The Cannes Brothers",
      "The Canal Brothers",
    ],
    question: "Who Opened The First Cinema In Paris In 1895?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "6239f8099129041bf3925cc0",
    correctAnswer: "Delta",
    allOptions: ["Dog", "Delta", "Danube", "Dig"],
    question:
      "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter D?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc83",
    correctAnswer: "Fipple",
    allOptions: ["Smicker", "Bibble", "Fipple", "Firman"],
    question:
      "Which word is defined as 'the mouthpiece of a recorder or similar wind instrument'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc62",
    correctAnswer: "Poppycock",
    allOptions: ["Dipthong", "Poppycock", "Ragamuffin", "Quomodocunquizing"],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'nonsense'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503d3",
    correctAnswer: "The Hula Hoop",
    allOptions: ["The Hula Hoop", "Rubix Cube", "Slinky", "Pog"],
    question:
      "What toy was released in 1957, creating an instant craze among children?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc55",
    correctAnswer: "Winklepicker",
    allOptions: ["Tittynope", "Dipthong", "Finifugal", "Winklepicker"],
    question:
      "Which word is defined as 'style of shoe or boot in the 1950s with a sharp and long pointed toe'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8b",
    correctAnswer: "Doodle Sack",
    allOptions: ["Doodle Sack", "Fipple", "Tittynope", "Quire"],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'Old English word for bagpipe'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc89",
    correctAnswer: "Dragoman",
    allOptions: ["Smicker", "Grommet", "Ragamuffin", "Dragoman"],
    question:
      "Which word is defined as 'an interpreter or professional guide for travelers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95031a",
    correctAnswer: "Robert Burns",
    allOptions: [
      "Robert Burns",
      "JM Barrie",
      "Robert Louis Stevenson",
      "James Hogg",
    ],
    question: "Who wrote Auld Lange Syne?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc73",
    correctAnswer: "Impignorate",
    allOptions: ["Dipthong", "Deipnophobia", "Impignorate", "Erf"],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'to pawn or mortgage something'?",
    tags: ["words"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc9a",
    correctAnswer: "Agastopia",
    allOptions: ["Dragoman", "Agastopia", "Oxter", "Jentacular"],
    question:
      "Which word is defined as 'admiration of a particular part of someoneâ€™s body'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc7f",
    correctAnswer: "Funambulist",
    allOptions: ["Funambulist", "Gubbins", "Kerfuffle", "Hullaballoo"],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'a tightrope walker'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "6239f82ea72e7a347ac879d4",
    correctAnswer: "Romeo",
    allOptions: ["Rwanda", "Roar", "Rowboat", "Romeo"],
    question:
      "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter R?",
    tags: ["language", "general_knowledge"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c6a",
    correctAnswer: "Little Jack Horner",
    allOptions: [
      "Humpty Dumpty",
      "Jack",
      "Happy Hungry Harry",
      "Little Jack Horner",
    ],
    question:
      "According to the nursery rhyme, who, 'sat in the corner eating a Christmas Pie''?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc84",
    correctAnswer: "Finifugal",
    allOptions: ["Groke", "Finifugal", "Gabelle", "Salopettes"],
    question: "Which word is defined as 'afraid of finishing anything'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe2c",
    correctAnswer: "Krona",
    allOptions: ["Franc", "Mark", "Krona", "Pund"],
    question:
      "Before the Euro, what was the basic unit of currency for Iceland?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "General Knowledge",
    id: "6239f8019129041bf3925cbd",
    correctAnswer: "Alpha",
    allOptions: ["Alpha", "Apple", "Animal", "Aeroplan"],
    question:
      "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter A?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const foodDrink = [
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951640",
    correctAnswer: "Sugar Cane",
    allOptions: ["Banana Tree", "Sugar Cane", "Tobacco", "Palm Tree"],
    question: "From which plant is Rum made?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "624ab0a5348a461bfc67068b",
    correctAnswer: "Africa",
    allOptions: [
      "The Middle East",
      "Central America",
      "Africa",
      "North America",
    ],
    question: "Where in the world are yams originally from?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951059",
    correctAnswer: "Melon",
    allOptions: ["Grape", "Apple", "Orange", "Melon"],
    question: "What Fruit Is A Cantaloupe?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950286",
    correctAnswer: "CourgetteÂ ",
    allOptions: ["CourgetteÂ ", "Carrot", "Onion", "Cucumber"],
    question: "What vegetable is known a zucchini in the USA?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "624ab0e1348a461bfc6706a2",
    correctAnswer: "Southeast Asia",
    allOptions: ["China", "Southeast Asia", "South America", "Central Asia"],
    question: "From which part of the world do oranges originate?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95029f",
    correctAnswer: "ParmesanÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Wensleydale", "Stilton", "ParmesanÂ ", "Gorgonzola"],
    question: "What sort of cheese would you sprinkle on spaghetti?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9515a2",
    correctAnswer: "ThreeÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Two", "Four", "Five", "ThreeÂ "],
    question: "How many pieces of bun are in a Mcdonald's Big Mac?",
    tags: ["food"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "624c60c095b12387e142c79b",
    correctAnswer: "Ramen",
    allOptions: ["Ramen", "Ceviche", "Plov", "Chilli Crab"],
    question: "Which of these dishes would you most expect to find in Japan?",
    tags: ["food"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95105c",
    correctAnswer: "Grapefruit",
    allOptions: ["Lemon", "Pineapple", "Grapefruit", "Blood Orange"],
    question: 'What fruit bears the latin name "citrus grandis"?',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502da",
    correctAnswer: "LambÂ ",
    allOptions: ["LambÂ ", "Beef", "Pork", "Chicken"],
    question: "Traditionally what type of meat is used to make a mousakka?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950299",
    correctAnswer: "PancakesÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Lamb", "Fish", "Simnel Cake", "PancakesÂ "],
    question: "What Traditionally Might You Eat On Shrove Tuesday?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "624ab077c64ce21c11f06e9e",
    correctAnswer: "South America",
    allOptions: ["The Middle East", "South America", "Central Asia", "Europe"],
    question: "From which part of the world do lima beans originate?",
    tags: ["food"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950242",
    correctAnswer: "BergamotÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Lavender", "Lemon", "BergamotÂ ", "Saffron"],
    question: "Which ingredient gives Earl Grey tea its distinctive flavour?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502c6",
    correctAnswer: "Spiced HamÂ ",
    allOptions: [
      "Special Made Artifial Meat",
      "Superior Manufactured Artificial Meat",
      "Special Ham",
      "Spiced HamÂ ",
    ],
    question: "What Is 'SPAM' Short For?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9502ec",
    correctAnswer: "DryÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Sweet", "DryÂ ", "Fruity", "Light"],
    question: "If A Sparkling Wine Is Labelled As 'Brut' How Will It Taste?",
    tags: ["drink"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f95029b",
    correctAnswer: "MozzarellaÂ ",
    allOptions: ["Gorgonzola", "Parmezan", "MozzarellaÂ ", "Gouda"],
    question: "What Type Of Cheese Is Traditionally Made From Buffaloes Milk?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "624c609150d1a5e051325a64",
    correctAnswer: "Moussaka",
    allOptions: ["Moussaka", "Verivorst", "Wiener Schnitzel", "Chicken Adobo"],
    question: "Which of these dishes is most associated with Greece?",
    tags: ["food"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950277",
    correctAnswer: "The United States",
    allOptions: ["Korea", "China", "Germany", "The United States"],
    question: "Where were fortune cookies invented?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950249",
    correctAnswer: "Avocado",
    allOptions: ["Mango", "Banana", "Avocado", "Pineapple"],
    question: "Which fruit has the most calories per gram?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Food & Drink",
    id: "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f951601",
    correctAnswer: "SturgeonÂ ",
    allOptions: ["SturgeonÂ ", "Salmon", "Trout", "Herring"],
    question: "Which fish does caviar come from? ",
    tags: ["fish", "food"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const filmTv = [
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc12",
    correctAnswer: '"What a dump."',
    allOptions: [
      '"May the odds ever be in your favor."',
      '"Weâ€™re goinâ€™ streaking!"',
      '"What a dump."',
      '"Mother of mercy, is this the end of Rico?"',
    ],
    question: "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Beyond the Forest'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb6c",
    correctAnswer: "Gentleman's Agreement",
    allOptions: [
      "Gentleman's Agreement",
      "The Bishop's Wife",
      "Crossfire",
      "Great Expectations",
    ],
    question: "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1947?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fae8",
    correctAnswer: "Paul Newman",
    allOptions: ["Dexter Gordon", "Paul Newman", "Bob Hoskins", "William Hurt"],
    question:
      "Who won the 1986 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Eddie Felson in The Color of Money?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc3e",
    correctAnswer: '"E.T. phone home."',
    allOptions: [
      '"There\'s no place like home."',
      '"Iâ€™ve been a poor man and Iâ€™ve been a rich man. And I choose rich every f****** time!"',
      '"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti."',
      '"E.T. phone home."',
    ],
    question:
      "Which of these quotes is from the film 'E.T.: The Extra-Terrestrial'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950788",
    correctAnswer: "George Clooney",
    allOptions: [
      "Sean Connery",
      "Gary Oldman",
      "George Clooney",
      "Ewan McGregor",
    ],
    question: "Which actor has featued in films including ER and Gravity?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950721",
    correctAnswer: "Kirsten Dunst",
    allOptions: [
      "Charlize Theron",
      "Emma Thompson",
      "Helen Mirren",
      "Kirsten Dunst",
    ],
    question:
      "Which actor has featued in films including Fargo and Spider-Man?",
    tags: ["acting", "film"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950618",
    correctAnswer: "Zoe Saldana",
    allOptions: [
      "Catherine Deneuve",
      "Zoe Saldana",
      "Audrey Hepburn",
      "Rachel Weisz",
    ],
    question:
      "Which actor has featued in films including Avengers: Endgame and Avatar?",
    tags: ["acting", "film"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbd0",
    correctAnswer: '"My precious."',
    allOptions: [
      '"My precious."',
      '"Keep your friends close, but your enemies closer."',
      '"You\'re gonna need a bigger boat."',
      '"You shall not pass!"',
    ],
    question:
      "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9507d1",
    correctAnswer: "Morgan Freeman",
    allOptions: [
      "Christopher Lee",
      "Liam Neeson",
      "Morgan Freeman",
      "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
    ],
    question:
      "Which actor has featued in films including Batman Begins and Lucy?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f950202",
    correctAnswer: "Michael Bay",
    allOptions: [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Michael Bay",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Martin Scorsese",
    ],
    question: "Which director directed Transformers?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950700",
    correctAnswer: "Sandra BÃ¦ Hovedr",
    allOptions: [
      "Charlize Theron",
      "Emma Thompson",
      "Maggie Smith",
      "Sandra BÃ¦ Hovedr",
    ],
    question: "Which actor has featued in films including Gravity and Speed?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950625",
    correctAnswer: "Jennifer Lawrence",
    allOptions: [
      "Jennifer Lawrence",
      "Catherine Deneuve",
      "Audrey Hepburn",
      "Rachel Weisz",
    ],
    question:
      "Which actor has featued in films including X-Men: Days of Future Past and American Hustle?",
    tags: ["acting", "film"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501f9",
    correctAnswer: "Peter Jackson",
    allOptions: [
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Woody Allen",
      "Peter Jackson",
      "Martin Scorsese",
    ],
    question:
      "Which director directed The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring?",
    tags: ["film"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f935",
    correctAnswer: "Sweet Smell of Success",
    allOptions: [
      "Network",
      "It's A Wonderful Life",
      "Sweet Smell of Success",
      "The Shining",
    ],
    question: "Which film contains the character 'J. J. Hunsecker'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950719",
    correctAnswer: "Kathy Bates",
    allOptions: ["Maggie Smith", "Helen Mirren", "Kate Winslet", "Kathy Bates"],
    question:
      "Which actor has featued in films including American Horror Story and Titanic?",
    tags: ["acting"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fafe",
    correctAnswer: "Sandra Bullock",
    allOptions: [
      "Sandra Bullock",
      "Helen Mirren",
      "Carey Mulligan",
      "Gabourey Sidibe",
    ],
    question:
      "Who won the 2009 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Leigh Anne Tuohy in The Blind Side?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa90",
    correctAnswer: "Viola Davis",
    allOptions: [
      "Naomie Harris",
      "Nicole Kidman",
      "Octavia Spencer",
      "Viola Davis",
    ],
    question:
      "Who won the 2016 Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress for playing the role of Rose Maxson in Fences?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc02",
    correctAnswer: '"I have always depended on the kindness of strangers."',
    allOptions: [
      '"A boy\'s best friend is his mother."',
      '"I have always depended on the kindness of strangers."',
      '"Oh what a day. What a lovely day!"',
      "\"Wait a minute, wait a minute. You ain't heard nothin' yet!\"",
    ],
    question:
      "Which of these quotes is from the film 'A Streetcar Named Desire'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb06",
    correctAnswer: "Helen Mirren",
    allOptions: ["PenÃ©lope Cruz", "Helen Mirren", "Judi Dench", "Meryl Streep"],
    question:
      "Who won the 2006 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of The Queen in The Queen?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Film & TV",
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f950797",
    correctAnswer: "Robert Downey Jr.",
    allOptions: [
      "Chris Evans",
      "Chris Hemsworth",
      "Robert Downey Jr.",
      "Tom Holland",
    ],
    question:
      "Which actor played the role of Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
    tags: ["acting", "film", "marvel", "comics", "mcu"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

const artsLiterature = [
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e98",
    correctAnswer: "Friedrich Schiller",
    allOptions: [
      "Sebastian Brant",
      "Agatha Christie",
      "Friedrich Schiller",
      "Rainer Maria Rilke",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Robbers'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501bf",
    correctAnswer: "The Great Gatsby",
    allOptions: [
      "The Shining",
      "The Great Gatsby",
      "The Silmarillion",
      "American Psycho (book)",
    ],
    question:
      "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'In my younger and more vulnerable years my father gave me some advice that Iâ€™ve been turning over in my mind ever since.'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f97b",
    correctAnswer: "All the King's Men",
    allOptions: [
      "Gone With the Wind",
      "Lonesome Dove",
      "Love in the Time of Cholera",
      "All the King's Men",
    ],
    question: "Which book contains the character 'Willie Stark'?",
    tags: ["literature"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f9fd",
    correctAnswer: "Sandro Botticelli",
    allOptions: [
      "Sandro Botticelli",
      "Leonardo da Vinci",
      "â€ŽSalvador DalÃ­",
      "â€ŽVincent van Gogh",
    ],
    question: 'Which artist painted "The Birth of Venus"',
    tags: ["painting", "art"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eba",
    correctAnswer: "Oscar Wilde",
    allOptions: [
      "Charles Dickens",
      "G. K. Chesterton",
      "Oscar Wilde",
      "Alphonse Daudet",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Happy Prince and Other Tales'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f5c",
    correctAnswer: "Isaac Asimov",
    allOptions: [
      "Isaac Asimov",
      "Ursula K. Le Guin",
      "Philip K. Dick",
      "Stephen King",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Pebble in the Sky'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ecb",
    correctAnswer: "Walter Scott",
    allOptions: [
      "Walter Scott",
      "Oscar Wilde",
      "J. R. R. Tolkien",
      "Alphonse Daudet",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Ivanhoe'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ec5",
    correctAnswer: "James Joyce",
    allOptions: [
      "Samuel Beckett",
      "Oscar Wilde",
      "Walter Scott",
      "Jonathan Swift",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Dubliners'?",
    tags: ["literature", "classic_novels"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f15",
    correctAnswer: "Giovanni Boccaccio",
    allOptions: [
      "Dante Alighieri",
      "Agatha Christie",
      "Stephenie Meyer",
      "Giovanni Boccaccio",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Decameron'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e14",
    correctAnswer: "Dan Brown",
    allOptions: ["Stephen King", "Donna Leon", "Dan Brown", "Frederik Pohl"],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Da Vinci Code'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e2d",
    correctAnswer: "L. Frank Baum",
    allOptions: [
      "L. Frank Baum",
      "Suzanne Collins",
      "James Fenimore Cooper",
      "Donna Leon",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Wonderful Wizard of Oz'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa08",
    correctAnswer: "Henri Rousseau",
    allOptions: [
      "Raphael",
      "â€ŽPablo Picasso",
      "Vasily Kandinsky",
      "Henri Rousseau",
    ],
    question: 'Which artist painted "The Sleeping Gypsy"',
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950dd4",
    correctAnswer: "Meg Cabot",
    allOptions: [
      "Stephenie Meyer",
      "Philip K. Dick",
      "Meg Cabot",
      "Brandon Sanderson",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Princess Diaries'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e41",
    correctAnswer: "Mikhail Bulgakov",
    allOptions: [
      "Mikhail Bulgakov",
      "Vladimir Nabokov",
      "Ayn Rand",
      "StanisÅ‚aw Lem",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'Heart of a Dog'?",
    tags: ["literature"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951094",
    correctAnswer: "Dog",
    allOptions: ["Horse", "Goat", "Dog", "Ghost"],
    question:
      'The only __________ to ever appear in a Shakespearean play was Crab in "The Two Gentlemen of Verona."',
    tags: ["shakespeare", "theater"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e1d",
    correctAnswer: "Marcel Proust",
    allOptions: [
      "FranÃ§ois-RenÃ© de Chateaubriand",
      "Umberto Eco",
      "Alexandre Dumas",
      "Marcel Proust",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'In Search of Lost Time'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fa30",
    correctAnswer: "Renaissance",
    allOptions: ["Art Nouveau", "Romanticism", "Cubism", "Renaissance"],
    question:
      "The Sistine Chapel ceiling painting by Michelangelo is a part of which art movement?",
    tags: ["art", "painting"],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501c3",
    correctAnswer: "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
    allOptions: [
      "The Sea of Monsters",
      "The Battle of the Labyrinth",
      "The Mysterious Island",
      "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
    ],
    question:
      "Which piece of written work starts with the line 'The two men appeared out of nowhere, a few yards apart in the narrow, moonlit lane.'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ed3",
    correctAnswer: "Walter Scott",
    allOptions: [
      "Walter Scott",
      "Oscar Wilde",
      "J. R. R. Tolkien",
      "Alphonse Daudet",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'The Heart of Midlothian'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
  {
    category: "Arts & Literature",
    id: "622a1c397cc59eab6f950dde",
    correctAnswer: "Mikhail Sholokhov",
    allOptions: [
      "Ivan Turgenev",
      "Henryk Sienkiewicz",
      "Mikhail Sholokhov",
      "Leo Tolstoy",
    ],
    question: "Which author wrote 'And Quiet Flows the Don'?",
    tags: [],
    type: "Multiple Choice",
  },
];

export {
  sportsLeisure,
  societyCulture,
  science,
  music,
  history,
  geography,
  generalKnowledge,
  foodDrink,
  filmTv,
  artsLiterature,
  availableCategories,
};
